<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Agriassitance</string>
    <string name="Acne">


    Subsistence agriculture occurs when farmers grow food crops to feed themselves and their families.
        In subsistence agriculture, farm output is targeted to survival and is mostly for local requirements with little or no surplus trade. The typical subsistence farm has a range of crops and animals needed by the family to feed and clothe themselves during the year.
        Planting decisions are made principally with an eye toward what the family will need during the coming year, and secondarily toward market prices. Tony Waters writes: “Subsistence peasants are people who grow what they eat, build their own houses, and live without regularly making purchases in the marketplace.
        " Despite the primacy of self-sufficiency in subsistence farming, today most subsistence farmers also participate in trade to some degree, though usually it is for goods that are not necessary for survival, and may include sugar, iron roofing sheets, bicycles, used clothing, and so forth.
        Most subsistence farmers today reside in developing countries. Although their amount of trade as measured in cash is less than that of consumers in countries with modern complex markets, many have important trade contacts and trade items that they can produce because of their special skills or special access to resources valued in the marketplace.
Subsistence farming or smallholder agriculture is when one family grows only enough to feed themselves. There is not usually much harvest to sell or trade, and what surplus there is tends to be stored to last the family until the next harvest. This is the most widely used method of agricultural farming in sub-Saharan Africa, and the majority of the rural poor depend on it for survival. It’s a method that has appeal to rural farmers because it allows food to be produced (with very little cost) in the rural areas, it lessens their need to find transportation to a city, and it creates opportunity to continue living in a village (where housing and land are much more affordable). It also means the family is self-sufficient in terms of food. Ideally, nothing needs to be purchased or borrowed from another source
    </string>

    <string name="measles">
       Shifting cultivation is an agricultural system in which plots of land are cultivated temporarily,
      then abandoned and allowed to revert to their natural vegetation while the cultivator moves on to another plot.
        The period of cultivation is usually terminated when the soil shows signs of exhaustion or, more commonly, when the field is overrun by weeds.
       The length of time that a field is cultivated is usually shorter than the period over which the land is allowed to regenerate by lying fallow.
                    This technique is often used in Less Economically Developed Countries or Low-income Countries).
                    In some areas, cultivators use a practice of slash-and-burn as one element of their farming cycle.

           Others employ land clearing without any burning, and some cultivators are purely migratory and do not use any cyclical method on a given plot.
                    Sometimes no slashing at all is needed where regrowth is purely of grasses, an outcome not uncommon when soils are near exhaustion and need to lie fallow.
                    In shifting agriculture, after two or three years of producing vegetable and grain crops on cleared land, the migrants abandon it for another plot.
                    Land is often cleared by slash-and-burn methods—trees, bushes and forests are cleared by slashing, and the remaining vegetation is burnt. The ashes add potash to the soil.
The estimated rate of deforestation in Southeast Asia in 1990 was 34,000 km² per year (FAO 1990, quoted in Potter 1993). In Indonesia alone it was estimated 13,100 km² per year were being lost, 3,680 km² per year from Sumatra and 3,770 km² from Kalimantan, of which 1,440 km² were due to the fires of 1982 to 1983. Since those estimates were made huge fires have ravaged Indonesian forests during the 1997 to 1998 El Niño associated drought.

Shifting cultivation was assessed by the FAO to be one of the causes of deforestation while logging was not. The apparent discrimination against shifting cultivators caused a confrontation between FAO and environmental groups, who saw the FAO supporting commercial logging interests against the rights of indigenous people (Potter 1993, 108). Other independent studies of the problem note that despite lack of government control over forests and the dominance of a political elite in the logging industry, the causes of deforestation are more complex. The loggers have provided paid employment to former subsistence farmers.
    </string>
    <string name="measle">
       A plantation is the large-scale estate meant for farming that specializes in cash crops. The crops that are grown include cotton, coffee, tea, cocoa, sugar cane, oil seeds, oil palms, fruits, rubber trees, and forest trees. Protectionist policies and natural comparative advantage have sometimes contributed to determining where plantations are located. A plantation house is the main house of a plantation, often a substantial farmhouse, which often serves as a symbol for the plantation as a whole. Plantation houses in the Southern United States and in other areas are known as quite grand and expensive architectural works today, though most were more utilitarian, working farmhouse.
                    The characteristic features of this type of farming are large estates or plantations, large capital investment, managerial and technical support, scientific methods of cultivation, single crop specialization, cheap labor, and a good system of transportation which links the estates to the factories and markets for the export of the products.
Industrial plantations are established to produce a high volume of wood in a short period of time. Plantations are grown by state forestry authorities (for example, the Forestry Commission in Britain) and/or the paper and wood industries and other private landowners (such as Weyerhaeuser, Rayonier and Sierra Pacific Industries in the United States, Asia Pulp  Paper in Indonesia). Christmas trees are often grown on plantations as well. In southern and southeastern Asia, teak plantations have recently replaced the natural forest.

Industrial plantations are actively managed for the commercial production of forest products. Industrial plantations are usually large-scale. Individual blocks are usually even-aged and often consist of just one or two species. These species can be exotic or indigenous. The plants used for the plantation are often genetically altered for desired traits such as growth and resistance to pests and diseases in general and specific traits, for example in the case of timber species, volumic wood production and stem straightness. Forest genetic resources are the basis for genetic alteration. Selected individuals grown in seed orchards are a good source for seeds to develop adequate planting material.
    </string>
    <string name="meas">
 Intensive farming or intensive agriculture is a kind of agriculture where a lot of money and labour are used to increase the yield that can be obtained per area of land. The use of large amounts of pesticides for crops, and of medication for animal stocks is common. This is a contrast to traditional agriculture, which does not get as much output per area. When agriculture is intensified, this means that the amount of work needed goes up, until the worker is replaced by a machine. At that point, there will only need to be a few workers to operate the machines. Intensive farming has often been done as a response to rising population levels. It is criticised, because the standards of animal welfare are low.[1] Intensive animal farming leads to increased pollution and to health issues.[2][3]

                    Modern day forms of intensive crop based agriculture involve the use of mechanical ploughing, chemical fertilizers, plant growth regulators or pesticides. It is associated with the increasing use of agricultural mechanization, which have enabled a substantial increase in production, yet have also dramatically increased environmental pollution by increasing erosion and poisoning water with agricultural chemicals.

    </string>
    <string name="hindi">
     Dry farming or Dry Land Farming refers to an improved system of cultivation whereby maximum amount of water is conserved by soil and water management.
                  Importance of Dry land Farming for India:
                    Considering the present rate of development of irrigation facilities and also water potentiality of the country, it is estimated that at any point of time 50% of cropped area in India will remain under Rainfed farming system. Such vast areas as of now consume hardly 25% of total fertilizer consumption
                    of the country. Due to poor level of management, crop productivity is also very low resulting in socio – economic backwardness of the people.
                    Types of Dryland Agriculture

Depending on the amount of rainfall received, dryland agriculture has been grouped into three categories:

Dry farming: it is production of crops without irrigation in areas where annual rainfall is less than 750 mm. Crop failures are more frequent under dry farming condition owing to prolonged dry spells during crop period. The growing season is less than 200 days. It is generally practiced in arid regions of the country.
</string>

    <string name="sh">
This can be different depending on the area you live in, so check what grows best in your area.  Some typical high-yield vegetables are tomato plants (especially cherry varieties), beans and peas, basil and other herbs, blueberries, leaf lettuce, kale, chard, spinach, carrots, peppers, and cucumbers.
    </string>
    <string name="pm">
    This can maximize your space and produce better yields than growing in rows.  There is less wasted space on pathways and you can fit more plants in a smaller area.  Be sure not to bunch them too tight though."))
</string>
    <string name="ncu">
    Vertical gardening can save a lot of space by growing up instead of out.  Many vertical growing crops are high yielding as well.  Beans and peas can be harvested as they are ready and will regrow quickly after they are plucked.  Using a trellis is typical.
</string>
    <string name="pmk">
     Pradhan Mantri Krishi Sinchai Yojana (PMKSY)",R.drawable.pmksy,"By packing the soil in box planters into an arc, more space is created than the dimensions of the box itself.  This allows more plants to be grown in the same amount of space a box planter takes up
</string>
    <string name="pkv">
   Using compost in your garden is extremely beneficial for the health of the plants.  Compost is very nutrient-rich, and plants grow stronger and yield more when compost is utilized in the garden
</string>
    <string name="enam">
   This makes efficient use of space and timing.  There are four basic approaches, and some can be combined:\n" +
                "\n" +
                " \n" +
                "\n" +
                "1. Two or more crops in succession (plant another crop in the same space after the previous one is harvested)\n" +
                "2. Same crop, successive plantings (stagger smaller plantings at timed intervals)\n" +
                "3. Two or more crops simultaneously (Non-competing crops, intercropping, and companion planting)\n" +
                "4. Same crop, different maturity dates (varieties with different maturity dates to ensure a continual harvest over the season)\n
</string>
    <string name="fert">
  a chemical or natural substance added to soil or land to increase its fertility.
Organic and Inorganic Fertilizers
Organic fertilizers are made from natural and organic materials—mainly manure, compost, or other animal and plant products. These fertilizers are a great source of nutrients, though there isn’t a measurable amount of any specific nutrients—some bags will print estimates. Organic fertilizers tend to work slowly and over the long-term. It can help to build up your soil over time. One of the best benefits of organic fertilizers is that is can be made at home. Using your own compost can help grow your garden!
Inorganic fertilizers are made of up chemical components that contain necessary nutrients. If you’re looking to give your garden a quick boost, this is likely the best option for you. For successful short-term growth, determine what nutrient your plant needs and use an inorganic fertilizer with nutrient.  
Nitrogen Fertilizers
Nitrogen is a plan nutrient responsible for growth. This ingredient is useful in fertilizers, particularly during the middle stages of a plant’s lifespan, when it needs encouragement to continue to grow large and stem new leaves. Both organic and inorganic fertilizers have sources of nitrogen in them.
Phosphate Fertilizers
Phosphorous is a nutrient that plants need continuously. Throughout their lifecycle, phosphorous help to strengthen the root system and stems of a plant. Flowering, seeding, and fruiting can all be improved with phosphorous.
Plants with a phosphorous deficiency will experience stunted growth. Phosphorous is long-lasting and slow acting. Using fertilizer in your soil before planting is generally a good idea.
Potassium Fertilizers
Potassium will help your plants to grow deeper and stronger roots. It can also help protect your plants from harm when they are deprived of other nutrients. This nutrient is vital for photosynthesis and has the ability to slow down any diseases that may infect your garden. Potassium fertilizer has a lot of benefits. The when and how of planting this fertilizer will depend on what you’re are planting. When you are using this fertilizer, place it as close to the roots as possible.
If there is a potassium deficiency in your plant, you may see yellowing or browning on the edges of leaves. Leaves will eventually die off if the deficiency continues.
</string>
    <string name="pesticides">
    Pesticides
Pesticides are substances that are meant to control pests, including weeds.[1] The term pesticide includes all of the following: herbicide, insecticides (which may include insect growth regulators, termiticides, etc.) nematicide, molluscicide, piscicide, avicide, rodenticide, bactericide, insect repellent, animal repellent, antimicrobial, and fungicide.[2] The most common of these are herbicides which account for approximately 80% of all pesticide use.[3] Most pesticides are intended to serve as plant protection products (also known as crop protection products), which in general, protect plants from weeds, fungi, or insects
Types of Pesticides
These are grouped according to the types of pests which they kill:
Grouped by Types of Pests They Kill
1.Insecticides – insects
2.Herbicides – plants
3.Rodenticides – rodents (rats and mice)
4.Bactericides – bacteria
5.Fungicides – fungi
6.Larvicides – larvae
</string>
    <string name="Medicinal">
    1. Basil

Basil health benefits:
Reduces stress
Strong antibacterial properties
Rich source of antioxidants
Prevents some harmful effects of aging
Reduces inflammation and swelling
Strengthens bones and liver
Boosts immunity
Boosts metabolism
Improves digestion
Common uses:
Sprinkle as a garnish for dishes
Include as ingredient for smoothies
2. Catnip

Catnip (nepeta cataria) is a fun plant for cats. Most cats are attracted to the plant and will roll around near it since its aroma acts as a stimulant. These medicinal plants also act as a sedative for cats if consumed. For humans, on the other hand, it is normally used as a stress reliever, sleep aid and a solution for skin issues. The majority of its health benefits come from the presence of nepetalactone, thymol and other compounds that make this plant great for you and your furry friend.
Catnip health benefits:
Repels bugs and relieves irritation from bug bites
Calms restlessness, anxiety and stress
Relieves stomach discomfort
Accelerates recovery from colds and fevers
3. Cayenne Pepper

Cayenne pepper (capsicum annuum) adds a spicy kick to any meal or drink and is a popular detoxifier for many people. Capsaicin is the compound responsible for cayenne’s spicy nature, but it’s also responsible for some of its health benefits. Some of these benefits include pain relief and lower cholesterol.
Cayenne pepper health benefits:
Detoxifies the body
Boosts metabolism
Eases an upset stomach and helps digestion
Improves circulation
Relieves pain
4.Garlic

Garlic (allium sativum) helps keep away vampires and unwanted diseases! This super plant is great for fighting infections, aiding with cholesterol management and much more. Eating garlic on a regular basis is good for your overall health and easy to incorporate into a wide array of dishes. Raw garlic is the most potent, so try eating it uncooked for the most health benefit.
Garlic health benefits:
Helps prevent heart disease
Lowers cholesterol and blood pressure
Prevents dementia, Alzheimer’s and similar degenerative diseases
Improves digestive health

5. Lemon Balm


Lemon balm (melissa officinalis) is a longstanding medicinal plant used to help relieve stress and ward off insects! An intense amount of stress can cause complications for many functions of the body, so minimal stress is ideal for a healthy functioning body. This lemony plant is delicious and easily used in several dishes like teas, ice cream and more. Many people consume lemon balm tea to help relieve anxiety, stress and even to calm restless kids.
Lemon balm benefits: Calms restlessness, anxiety and stress
Reduces inflammation
Treats cold sores
Soothes menstrual cramps
Common uses:
Brew leaves for a tea
Garnish for dishes and desserts
Apply tea or essential oil topically
6.	Parsley
https://www.proflowers.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/medicinal-plants-11-parsley.jpg
Parsley health benefits:
Relieves bloating and supports digestive health
Fights bad breath
Supports bone health
Rich source of antioxidants
Common uses:
Sprinkle as a garnish for dishes
Create a juice or brew for a tea
</string>
    <string name="yield">
        Plant High-Yielding Crops

This can be different depending on the area you live in, so check what grows best in your area.  Some typical high-yield vegetables are tomato plants (especially cherry varieties), beans and peas, basil and other herbs, blueberries, leaf lettuce, kale, chard, spinach, carrots, peppers, and cucumbers

        Plant in Blocks or Triangles

 Plant in Blocks or Triangles This can maximize your space and produce better yields than growing in rows.  There is less wasted space on pathways and you can fit more plants in a smaller area.  Be sure not to bunch them too tight though

   Vertical Gardening

 Vertical gardening can save a lot of space by growing up instead of out.  Many vertical growing crops are high yielding as well.  Beans and peas can be harvested as they are ready and will regrow quickly after they are plucked.  Using a trellis is typical

        Arching the Soil in Box Planters

   By packing the soil in box planters into an arc, more space is created than the dimensions of the box itself.  This allows more plants to be grown in the same amount of space a box planter takes up

   Use Compost

     Using compost in your garden is extremely beneficial for the health of the plants.  Compost is very nutrient-rich, and plants grow stronger and yield more when compost is utilized in the garden
      This makes efficient use of space and timing.  There are four basic approaches, and some can be combined:\n" +
                \n +
                 \n +
                \n+
                1. Two or more crops in succession (plant another crop in the same space after the previous one is harvested)\n +
                2. Same crop, successive plantings (stagger smaller plantings at timed intervals)\n+
                3. Two or more crops simultaneously (Non-competing crops, intercropping, and companion planting)\n +
                4. Same crop, different maturity dates (varieties with different maturity dates to ensure a continual harvest over the season)\n
</string>
    <string name="BlackSpot">
Black spot is an infectious fungal disease that affects most types of roses, though some species are more resistant than others to this particular disease.

         Characteristics

Black Spot resembles black splotches, which then develop leaf yellowing around the spots. Black spot typically occurs during moist, humid conditions and are usually wind-borne and rain splashed to newly emerging leaf tissue. Using a product, will cure your roses of black spot to ensure they are healthy all season long!

Symptoms of Black Spot Damage

        Black Spot looks like black splotches which then develop leaf yellowing around them.
Plants infected with Black Spot can experience any of the following results:
Yellowing of leaves or tissue death
Premature leaf drop
General decline in the growth and vigour of the plant
</string>

    <string name="Botrytisblight">
There are several types of Botrytis Blight and the most common forms thrive in cool rainy weather.
Botrytis Blight can attack all parts of the plant except the roots.
Common symptoms include:
Brown plant tissue
Blight bumps or cankers
Fruit or bulb rot or end rot
So  What is Botrytis Blight?
Botrytis Blight, which is sometimes known as gray mold, is a fungal disease. Blight is a rapid and complete chlorosis or yellowing and then death of plant tissues. The yellowing is due to a failure to develop chlorophyll, caused by a nutrient deficiency. There are several types of Botrytis Blight and the most common forms thrive in cool rainy weather.

Characteristics

Typically Botrytis Blight is brown or spotted plant “dust” that may have silver spores on the dead or dying tissue. It can affect any part of the plant except the roots. While this can be a deathly disease for plants, you can ensure the long term health of your plant by using a product, to treat blight on first appearance.

Symptoms of Botrytis Blight Damage

Plants infected with Botrytis Blight can have any of the following symptoms (depending on the plant species).
Leaf spots or blights (brown dying tissue)
Cankers (bumps) or Shoot Blights
Bud Blast – withering or dropping of buds from otherwise healthy plants
Flower Blights
Fruit or Bulb Rot or end rot
</string>
    <string name="LeafSpot">
Leaf Spot is a commonly used descriptor for identifying many plant diseases. In larger clusters or rows, leaf spot can also be known as anthracnose or canker.
Leaves infected with leaf spot will yellow and may drop prematurely. The fungal blight can sustain itself and reproduce in the dead debris of the plant.  to quickly eliminate leaf spot and bring health back to your plants!
So What is Leaf Spot?
Leaf Spot is a commonly used descriptor for identifying many different plant diseases. Most leaf spot is fungal but some is also caused by bacteria. Often the larger clusters of fungal leaf spot are referred to as anthracnose or canker.

Characteristics

Leaf Spots are typically brown, but depending on the type of fungus, the spot could also be tan or black. Concentric rings or dark margins around the spot may also be present. Over time the spots can group together to form blotches and sometimes they are formed in angular patterns on the plant.
Using a product such as Safer® Brand Garden Fungicide will prevent further spread and actually eliminate the leaf spot all together!
Symptoms of Leaf Spot Damage
Leaves infected with leaf spot will yellow and may drop prematurely. The fungal blight can sustain itself and reproduce in the dead debris of the plant. This will cause the disease to further spread and possibly infect other plants.
Safer® Brand Garden Fungicide can ensure that your plants do not remain infected and stay healthy all season long.



</string>
    <string name="PowderyMildew">
Powder Mildew

Powdery mildew is typically white or gray and resides on the leaf surface. Sometimes when it first appears, it is mistaken for dust or dirt. When touched, some of the powder will rub off.
Depending on the type of plant, powdery mildew break out could have mild to severely damaging effects. With the damaging effects that powdery mildew can have on your plants, it is essential for powdery mildew treatment to use a product, such as OMRI® Listed Safer® Brand Garden Fungicide.
So What is Powdery Mildew?
There are numerous strains of fungi that are commonly referred to as powdery mildew. They typically have similar habitats and similar methods can be used to control them.
Characteristics
Powdery mildew is typically white or gray on the leaf surface. Sometimes when it first appears it is mistaken for dust or dirt. When touched, some of it will rub off. Lower leaves are the most affected but it can be found on the entire plant. If left untreated, powdery mildew can take over the entire plant. Using Safer® Brand Garden Fungicide for your powdery mildew treatment will keep your plants healthy and help control powdery mildew.
 
Symptoms of Powdery Mildew Damage

Plants infected with powdery mildew can have any of the following symptoms (depending on the plant species).
The disease is taking needed nutrients away from the plant and the following can result:
Stunting or distortion of leaves, buds, growing tips and fruit
Yellowing of leaves or tissue death
Premature leaf drop
General decline in the growth and vigor of the plant


</string>
    <string name="Rust">
Rust

It’s not the same rust that you see on metal. There are over 5000 known species of rust found on plants. They are fungi that travel through the air to settle on a host plant.
Some of the common symptoms of rust include defoliation, stunted growth or branch dieback.

        So What is Rust?

It’s not the same rust that you see on metal. There are over 5000 known species of rust found on plants. They are fungi that travel through the air to settle on a host plant.
 
Characteristics

Rust is typically brownish-yellow to bright orange spots that form on leaves. The spots are filled with a powdery substance. This substance contains the spores that will spread to other plants if not treated.
 
Symptoms of Rust
Plants that have rust growth will not directly die from this type of fungi, but it can contribute the decline of the plant.
Some of the common symptoms include defoliation, stunted growth or branch dieback. Leaving your plant exposed to rust will surely infect other plants since rust is easily spread through the air.


</string>
<string name="Germs">
Germs live everywhere. You can find germs (microbes) in the air; on food, plants and animals in soil and water — on just about every other surface, including your body.

Most germs won\t harm you. Your immune system protects you against infectious agents. However some germs are formidable adversaries because they\re constantly mutating to breach your immune system defenses. Knowing how germs work can increase your chances of avoiding infection.
 Infectious agents: From bacteria to worms
Different types of infectious agents
Types of infectious agents

Infectious agents come in a variety of shapes and sizes. Categories include:

Bacteria
Viruses
Fungi
Protozoans
Helminths
        Bacteria
Bacteria are one-celled organisms visible only with a microscope. They\re so small that if you lined up a thousand of them end to end, they could fit across the end of a pencil eraser.

Not all bacteria are harmful, and some bacteria that live in your body are helpful. For instance, Lactobacillus acidophilus — a harmless bacterium that resides in your intestines — helps you digest food, destroys some disease-causing organisms and provides nutrients.

Many disease-causing bacteria produce toxins — powerful chemicals that damage cells and make you ill. Other bacteria can directly invade and damage tissues. Some infections caused by bacteria include:

Strep throat
Tuberculosis
Urinary tract infections
Viruses
Viruses are much smaller than cells. In fact, viruses are basically just capsules that contain genetic material. To reproduce, viruses invade cells in your body, hijacking the machinery that makes cells work. Host cells are often eventually destroyed during this process.

Viruses are responsible for causing numerous diseases, including:

AIDS
Common cold
Ebola hemorrhagic fever
Genital herpes
Influenza
Measles
Chickenpox and shingles
Antibiotics designed for bacteria have no effect on viruses.

Fungi
There are many varieties of fungi, and we eat quite a few of them. Mushrooms are fungi, as is the mold that forms the blue or green veins in some types of cheese. And yeast, another type of fungus, is a necessary ingredient in most types of bread.

Other fungi can cause illness. One example is candida — a yeast that can cause infection. Candida can cause thrush — an infection of the mouth and throat — in infants and in people taking antibiotics or who have an impaired immune system. Fungi are also responsible for skin conditions such as athletes foot and ringworm.

Protozoans
Protozoans are single-celled organisms that behave like tiny animals — hunting and gathering other microbes for food. Many protozoans call your intestinal tract home and are harmless. Others cause diseases, such as:

Giardia
Malaria
Toxoplasmosis
Protozoans often spend part of their life cycles outside of humans or other hosts, living in food, soil, water or insects. Some protozoans invade your body through the food you eat or the water you drink. Others, such as malaria, are transmitted by mosquitoes.

Helminths

Helminths are among the larger parasites. The word helminth comes from the Greek word for worm.If this parasite — or its eggs — enters your body, it takes up residence in your intestinal tract, lungs, liver, skin or brain, where it lives off your bodys nutrients. Helminths include tapeworms and roundworms.
</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
